A Finding Aid to the Leo Castelli Gallery Records, circa 1880-2000, bulk 1957-1999, in the Archives of American Art AAA.leocast
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1948-1999, bulk 1957-1997; Series 1; (Boxes 1-23, 191, OVs 233-236; 24.6 linear feet)
  - Escobar, Marisol - Announcements, 1957, 1960; (Oversized material from Box 9, Folder 10) (Box OV 236)
  - Ileana Sonnabend Galerie - Envelope, 1963; (Oversized material from Box 11, Folder 70) (Box OV 236)
  - Ileana Sonnabend Galerie - Floor Plans, 1966; (Oversized material from Box 11, Folder 71) (Box OV 236)
  - International Contemporary Art Fair - Floor Plans, 1976-1977; (Oversized material from Box 12, Folder 9) (Box OV 236)
  - Langlais, Bernard (Artist), 1960-1965; (Oversized material from Box 13, Folder 44) (Box OV 236)
  - Namuth, Hans - Bruce Nauman Drawings, circa 1994; (Oversized material from Box 15, Folder 31) (Box OV 235)
  - Nauman, Bruce, 1973; (Oversized material from Box 15, Folder 35) (Box OV 236)
  - Rosenquist, James - Horse Blinders, circa 1969-1970; (Oversized material from Box 18, Folder 3) (Box OV 236)
  - Rosenquist, James - Daniel Saxon-Lee Gallery Floor Plans, circa 1985-1986; (Oversized material from Box 18, Folder 4) (Box OV 233)
  - Ruscha, Ed - "Books", circa 1972; (Oversized material from Box 18, Folder 17) (Box OV 236)
- Administrative Files, 1941-1999, bulk 1970s-1990s; Series 2; (Boxes 24-39, 192-193, OVs 237-238; 16.8 linear feet)
  Administrative Files document a wide variety of the gallery's activities and business. Essentially, these are files that were arranged by the gallery according to subject or topic and cover almost all activities except specific exhibitions. These files include records and correspondence about buildings and space, advertising, appraisals, auctions, consignments, loans, miscellaneous business correspondence, index cards, business arrangements with artists, information about many artists, interviews with artists (transcripts), history of the gallery, mailings, photograph requests, shipping, and other topics. There are staff notebooks and files and Leo Castelli's notebooks and notes from the late 1950s through the early 1990s. Extensive outgoing chronological correspondence filed in this series dates from 1964-1977. Also found are transcripts of interviews with Leo Castelli, biographical material, and scattered photographs.
  Researchers should note that the Administrative Files often overlap and complement the General Correspondence. However, they focus slightly more distinctly on gallery business activities and are arranged mostly by subject or topic, except for the chronological business correspondence. Researchers are encouraged to reference both series. For example, correspondence with and about Jasper Johns may be found in both series, but the administrative files most likely focus on a specific loan, consignment, or business activity or transaction.
  - 4 East 77th Street - Alterations to Building, 1961-1962; (Oversized material housed in OV 247) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 4 East 77th Street - Lease, 1976-1989 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - 1894 Application for Erection of Building (Photostat), circa 1958-1962; (Oversized material housed in Box 193, Folder 1) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Building Remodel, 1958-1959 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Contracts, 1959-1962 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Correspondence, 1956-1962 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Correspondence, Ann Nollen, 1941-1942; (Oversized material housed in Box 193, Folder 2) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Correspondence with Tenants, 1959-1961 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Directors Meetings, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Eve Briscoe, 1959-1962 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Gallery Zoning, 1960-1961; (Oversized material housed in Box 193, Folder 3) (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - John J. Blesch Real Estate Monthly Statements, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - John J. Blesch Real Estate Monthly Statements, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Lease, 1959, 1962 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Legal Documents, 1942 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Miscellaneous, 1948-circa 1962 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Permits, 1958-1961 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Property Assessment, 1960-1961 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Sale, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - 4 East 77th Street (Maveri Corp.) - Services, 1959-1960 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - 85 Quay Street, Brooklyn, NY, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - 142 Greene Street - Lease, 1979-1990 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - 166 South First Street, Brooklyn, NY - Lease, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - 166 South First St., Brooklyn, NY (Overbridge Assoc.) - Lease, 1991-1996 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - 528-530 W. Broadway Blueprints, 1961-1963; (Oversized material housed in OV 248 and separated due to water damage) (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - 568-578 Broadway - Elevator Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - 568-578 Broadway - Lease, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Address Book - Susan Brundage, circa 1980s (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Addresses and Business Cards, circa 1973-1975; 3 Folders (Box 24, Folder 29-31)
  - Advertising, 1959-1964 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Advertising, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Advertising, 1991, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Advertising, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Advertising - European, 1960-1964 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Advertising - New York Post, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Advertisement Proofs, 1965-1966 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Advertising Rates, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Appraisals, 1963-1967 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Appraisals, 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Appraisals, 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Appraisals, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Art Catalogs Offerings, circa 1992 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Artist Applications, 1957-1961 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Artists' Biographies, circa 1957-1963 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Artists' Biographies, 1992-1997; (3 folders; includes 3 computer discs) (Box 25, Folder 5-7)
  - Artschwager, Richard - Group and One Man Shows, 1967-1969 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Auction Catalog 1988-1996: Artschwager-Kelly, circa 1997 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Auction Catalog 1988-1996: Kosuth-Salle, circa 1997 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Auction Catalog 1988-1996: Serra-Weiner, circa 1997 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Auction Results - Sotheby's, 1994, May (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Auction Results [Binder 1]: Artschwager-Lichtenstein, circa 1996 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Auction Results [Binder 1]: Morris-Therrien, circa 1996 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Auction Results [Binder 1]: Twombly-Weiner, circa 1996 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Auction Results [Binder 2]: Artschwager-Flavin, circa 1999 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Auction Results [Binder 2]: Johns-Warhol, circa 1999 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Auction Results [Binder 2]: Miscellaneous, circa 1999 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Authentication - Andy Warhol, 1970, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Authentication Requests, 1971, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Balog, Michael - Registry, circa 1970-1974 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Barry, Robert - Inventory, 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Barry, Robert - Transfer, 1970, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Berri, Claude - Interview Correspondence, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Berri, Claude - Interview Transcript (in French), Cassettes 1-3, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Berri, Claude - Interview Transcript (in French), Part II, 1990; 2 Folders (Box 25, Folder 26-27)
  - Berri, Claude - Interview Transcript (in French), Part III, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Berri, Claude - "Claude Berri rencontre Leo Castelli" by Ann Hindry, circa 1987-1990 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Berri, Claude - "Claude Berri rencontre Leo Castelli" by Ann Hindry - Original Copy, circa 1987-1990 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Berri, Claude - "Claude Berri rencontre Leo Castelli, marchand d'art" Press Material (in French), 1989 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Berri, Claude - "Claude Berri rencontre Leo Castelli" Text, circa 1987-1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Bontecou, Lee - Collections Information, circa 1960s (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Brochures and Flyers, circa 1991-1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Brochures and Flyers - Air Freight, 1989-circa 1995 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Brochures and Flyers - Crating, circa 1991-1995 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Brochures and Flyers - Food and Drink for Openings, circa 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Brochures and Flyers - Transport in New York, circa 1991-1995 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Brochures and Flyers - Transport Out of State and International, circa 1991-1995 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Brown, James - Consignments, 1989-1994 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Brown, James - Inventory Lists, circa 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Calle, Sophie, circa 1994 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Cane, Louis, circa 1982 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Castelli, Leo - Biographical Information, circa 1980s (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Castelli, Leo - Business Cards, circa 1978-1982 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Castelli, Leo - Interview with Alan Jones, circa early 1980s (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Castelli, Leo - Interview with Louis Zona, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Castelli, Leo - Interview with Voice of America, Oct 2, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Castelli, Leo - Lecture Slides Lists, circa 1982 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Castelli, Leo - Loft Blueprints, 1978; (Oversized material housed in OV 249) (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Castelli, Leo - Miscellaneous Memorabilia, circa 1978-1982; (1 shoebox) (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Castelli Tapes and Films Rental Invoices - Examples and Blanks, circa 1991-1995 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Chamberlain, John, circa 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Chamberlain, John, circa 1973 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Chamberlain, John - Collections Information, circa 1960s (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Chia, Sandro, circa 1984 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Chryssa, circa 1990s (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Clients for Consideration, 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Computer Manuals, circa 1989-1993 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Computer Manuals, circa 1989-1999; (Includes 1 computer disc) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Computer Manuals - Art Stacks, 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Computer Manuals - Art Stacks, circa 1992-1997 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Computer Repairs, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Condition Reports, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Consignments - Returns, 1958-1966 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Copyright Information, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Copyright Requests, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Daphnis, Nassos, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Daphnis, Nassos - Collections Information, circa 1960s (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Daphnis, Nassos - Loan and Collection Information, circa 1967-1969 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Darboven, Hanne, 1992-1995 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Darboven, Hanne - Biographical Information, circa 1988 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Darboven, Hanne - Shipping, 1990-1995 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Day Books - Sutherland, Nina, 1964-1965 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Day Books - Sutherland, Nina, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Day Books - Sutherland, Nina, circa 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Day Planner, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Day Planner, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Day Planner, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Day Planner, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Day Planner, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Day Planner, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Day Planner - Leo Castelli, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Day Planner - John Good, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Day Planner - John Good, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Day Planner - John Good [?], 1985 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Day Planner - John Good [?], 1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Day Planner - John Good [?], 1987 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Day Planner - Michael Ortoleva [?], 1989 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Day Planner - Dorothy Spears [?], 1988 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Day Planner - Dorothy Spears [?], 1989 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Dead Files, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Dead Files, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Dead Files, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Dibbets, Jan, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Dzubas, Friedel - Price Lists, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Employees - Tejas Englesmith, 1971-1974 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Employees - Charlene Langos, 1993-1997 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Employees - Laura Marie Leopardo, 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Employees - Maureen Mahony, 1989, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Employees - [Susan Brundage?], 1973 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Employees - Susan Brundage, 1991-1997 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - European Summer Travel, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Expired Lease Agreements, 1974, 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Flavin, Dan - Price List, circa 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Flood Damage, 1970-1973 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence, 1962-1976 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence, 1983-1990 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - General Correspondence, 1991; 2 Folders (Box 29, Folder 1-2)
  - General Correspondence, 1992; 5 Folders (Box 29, Folder 3-7)
  - General Correspondence, 1993; 3 Folders (Box 29, Folder 8-10)
  - General Correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - General Requests, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - General Requests, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Grisi, Laura, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Higgins, Edward - Collections Information, circa 1960s (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Higgins, Edward - Registry, circa late 1960s (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Ideas for the New Magazine, circa 1950s-1970s (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Index Cards - Artist Bibliographies, circa 1960-1967; (1 shoebox) (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Index Cards - Collectors and Individuals, circa 1980s-1997; (2 shoeboxes) (Box 30, Folder 2-3)
  - Index Cards - Critics and Publications, circa 1980s-1997; (1 shoebox) (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Index Cards - Exhibitions and Clients Interest, circa 1981-1985; (1 shoebox) (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Index Cards - Gallery Rolodex, circa 1980s-1997; (1 shoebox) (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Index Cards - Institutions and Corporations, circa 1980s-1997; (2 shoeboxes) (Box 31, Folder 4-5)
  - Job Applications, 1957, 1963-1969 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Job Applications, 1971-1975 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Johns, Jasper, 1993-1995 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Johns, Jasper - Biographical Information, circa 1959-1969, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Johns, Jasper - Collections Information, circa 1960s (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Johns, Jasper - Loans, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Johns, Jasper - Wall Type/ULAE, 1996; (Includes 1 computer disc) (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Cletus, 1981-1990 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Joint Ventures - BlumHelman, 1974, 1984-1986 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Joint Ventures - Sal's Rolling Chassis, 1986-1987 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Judd, Donald - Business, 1969-1977 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Judd, Donald - Loan Receipts, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Judd, Donald - Questions, circa 1969-1977 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Kennedy, Mame, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Klein, Yves, 1982-1983 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Kosuth, Joseph, 1991-1993 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Krueger, Jack - Biographical Information, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Labels, circa 1960s-1980s (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Landsman, Stanley - Biographical Information, circa 1970 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Leo Castelli Gallery Daily Log, circa 1966-1967; (Removed material housed in Box 192, Folder 1) (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Leo Castelli Gallery Floor Plans (142 Greene St.), circa 1970s-1980s; (Oversized material housed in OV 250) (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Leo Castelli Gallery Floor Plans (420 W. Broadway), circa 1971; (Oversized material housed in OV 251) (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Leo Castelli Gallery History, circa 1980s (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Leo Castelli Gallery Information, circa 1992 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Leo Castelli Publications and Exhibition Catalogs - Inventory, circa 1970s-1987 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Letters of Recommendation, 1988-1996 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1992-1996 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy - Airplane (RL 1109), circa 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy - Provenance, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Lichtenstein, Roy - Shipping, 1992-1995 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Lists of Contacts, circa 1990 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Loans Completed, 1957-1959 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Loans Completed, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Loans Completed, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Loans Completed, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Loans Completed, 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Loans Completed, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Loans Completed, 1965-1966 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Loans Completed, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Loans Completed, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Loans Completed, 1968-1969 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Loans Completed, 1970-1971 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Loans Completed, 1971-1972 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Loans Completed, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Loans Completed, 1989-1991 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Loans (General), 1964-1966 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Loans (General), 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Loans (General), 1974 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Loans (General), circa 1997 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Loans - Photographs, to be Returned, 1990-1992 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Mailing Lists, 1962-1964 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Mailing Lists, circa 1970s-1990s; (Oversized material housed in Box 193, Folder 4) (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Mailing Lists, circa 1971-1973 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Mailing Lists - Chicago, circa 1960s (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Mailing Lists - Los Angeles, circa 1960s (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Material Requests, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Material Requests, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Material Requests, 1966; 2 Folders (Box 34, Folder 27-28)
  - Material Requests, 1967; (3 folders; Removed material housed in Box 192, Folders 2-3) (Box 35, Folder 1-3)
  - Material Requests, 1968; (2 folders; Removed material housed in Box 192, Folders 4-5) (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
  - Material Requests, 1969; (2 folders; Removed material housed in Box 192, Folders 6-7) (Box 35, Folder 6-7)
  - Membership Cards, 1979-1981 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Morris, Robert, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Morris, Robert - Business, 1973-1976, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Nauman, Bruce - Biographical Information, circa 1994 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Nauman, Bruce - Business, circa 1971 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Nauman, Bruce - Interview and Essay by Christopher Cordes, circa 1989; 2 Folders (Box 35, Folder 13-14)
  - Nauman, Bruce - Permissions, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Noland, Kenneth - Biographical Information, circa 1973 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Noland, Kenneth - Registry, circa 1969-1979 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Notebook, circa 1957-1958 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Notebook, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Notebook, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Notebook, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, circa 1974-1988 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, March 31 - September, 1974[?] (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, September 18, 1974 - January, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, February 4 - June 20, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, July 2 - November 11, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, November 12, 1975 - February 23, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, February 28 - May 17, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, May 18 - September 30, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, circa 1976, November - 1977, May (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, 1977, May - 1978, January (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, 1978[?], January-May (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, 1978, December - 1979 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, circa 1979, June-October (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, circa 1979, September - 1980, June (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, circa September 15, 1981 - 1982 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, September 8, 1982 - 1983 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, circa 1983 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, circa late 1983 - 1984 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, 1984, September - 1985 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, circa 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, circa 1986, July - 1987, January (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, 1987, February-July (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, October 7, 1987 - May, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Notebook - Leo Castelli, circa 1988, June-July (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Notes, circa 1960s (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Notes, circa 1991-1995 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Notes - 1966-1967 Season, circa 1966-1967 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Notes - Leo Castelli, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Notes - Miscellaneous, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Notes - Miscellaneous Office, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Notes - Projects in Progress, circa 1987 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Offering Lists, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Office Supplies, circa 1991-1995 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Oldenburg, Claes - Inventory, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Oldenburg, Claes - Questions, circa 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1964, November (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1964, December (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1965, January (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1965, February (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1965, March (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1965, April (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1965, May (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1965, June (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1965, July (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1965, August (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1965, September (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1965, October (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1965, November (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1965, December (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1966, January (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1966, February (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1966, March (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1966, April (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1966, May (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1966, June (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1966, July (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1966, August (Box 36, Folder 43)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1966, September (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1966, October (Box 36, Folder 45)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1966, November (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1966, December (Box 36, Folder 47)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1967, January (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1967, February (Box 36, Folder 49)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1967, March (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1967, April (Box 36, Folder 51)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1967, May (Box 36, Folder 52)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1967, June (Box 36, Folder 53)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1967, July (Box 36, Folder 54)
  - Outgoing Chronological Files, 1967, September (Box 36, Folder 55)